# Jennifer Quintal

# Full Stack Developer

**★** jenniferalexandria.ca

#### **Profile**

I'm a full-stack web developer experienced in operations and experiential marketing. With a passion for following market trends, and building vendor relationships, I have a proven passion for implementing strategic initiatives, creating and developing products to fulfil client needs

#### Skills

Languages (JavaScript, HTML, CSS, SQL, Ruby),

Frameworks & Libraries (NodeJS, React, Next.js, Ajax, Express, EJS, jQuery, Bootstrap, Rails),

Systems & Databases (PostgreSQL, Git), Testing (Jest, Storybook, Cypress, RSpec),

Additional Skills (Microsoft Office, SalesForce, Softrip, Negotiations, Budgets & Reporting, Communication & Presenting, Leadership)

# **Projects**

**Route Roamer,** an application where users can create an

Apr 2023

AI-generated, personalized travel itinerary for anywhere around the world and suggested activities will appear on Google Maps *∂* 

• Tech Stack: React, Next, ChatGPT API, Google Maps API, Mapbox API, PostgreSQL

**Jungle**, a mini e-commerce application where users can view and purchase products in a secure environment using the Stripe API. ∂ Apr 2023

• Tech Stack: Ruby, Rails, Stripe API, PostgreSQL

JNMaps - WikiMap, an application where using Google Maps API, users can create, view and modify maps *∂* 

Mar 2023

• Tech Stack: Node, Express, Sass, Google Maps

# **Education**

**Lighthouse Labs,** *Diploma: Full-Stack Web Development* 

2023 | Vancouver

York University, Bachelor of Arts: English

2013 - 2016 | Toronto

**Concordia University,** *Major: Joint Specialization in Anthropology* 

2011 – 2013 | Montreal

& Sociology Minor: English Literature

## **Employment**

### Polar Client Experience Advisor, Quark Expeditions

Nov 2021 - Nov 2022 | Remote

- Modified client accounts to support their needs
- Liaise between clients and Sales team

#### Senior Operations Coordinator, WorldStrides Explorica

Oct 2018 – Sep 2020 | Toronto

- Acting manager for 6 months, managing a team of four
- Created and developed new initiatives and products
- Collaborated with various senior stakeholders
- Negotiating and contracting competitive rates
- Analyzed reporting and operational stats to ensure goals are being met and surpassed